tulababycarriers.com 2018-11-27

# Baby Tula - Privacy Policy

Baby Tula values you as a customer and respects your privacy. We collect certain information from you that allows us to customize and enhance your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions. Please carefully review this policy to learn about how we collect, use, protect, and share personal information you provide us and your choices for managing this information.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Baby Tula website (the “Site”), which is owned and operated by Baby Tula, LLC. (“Baby Tula”, “us”, or “we”), and is incorporated into our Terms of Use and therefore governs your use of our Site. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of this information. By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.

We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any websites not operated by Baby Tula, to which our Site links, or that link to our Site.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

We collect information from you in several different ways. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

  * Help make our Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * Help you quickly find information, products, and services.
  * Help us create and share content that is most relevant to you.
  * Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.

Registration and Ordering

Before using certain parts of our Site or ordering products, you may need to complete an online registration form. During registration, you will be prompted to provide to us certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, we may also ask you for your country of residence and/or your organization’s country of operation, so we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and for your gender. This information is used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, your personal information may be used to contact you.

Email Addresses  
Our Site permits you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to  request us to notify you of new products or styles or availability and to sign up for email newsletters and special offers.

Cookies and Other Technology  
Like many Sites, Baby Tula employs cookies and web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or “action tags”) to speed your navigation of our Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track Site usage.

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of our Site. We must use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase.  Baby Tula cookies do not and cannot infiltrate a user’s hard drive to gather a user’s confidential information.  Our cookies are not “spyware.”

Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on the Baby Tula website has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on the Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon.

We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor our content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us.

Log Files  
As is true of most websites, the Baby Tula Site automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access it. We may also log your Internet protocol (“IP”) address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.)

Age  
We respect children’s privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.

Geographic Location  
Baby Tula may use the GPS feature of your mobile device to determine your geographic location. This information is used to provide you with the address of, and directions to, the nearest  location of Baby Tula or other location-dependent features. If you would prefer that we not know your geographic location, you may disable or decline the function when you first use our site, (or later, if your mobile device allows you to change the settings after initial download).

#### INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE

Internal Use  
We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve Site content and layout, to improve outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to the Site. In order to facilitate such use and the other use described in this Section 2, we may share your information with affiliates under our control.

Communications with You  
We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our services and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for to register for a contest or sweepstakes; to request us to notify you of new products or styles or availability; to sign up for email newsletters and special offers. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver the information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails (see the opt out section, below, for more details). Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders.

External Use  
We want to provide you with excellent service and to offer you a great selection. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone other than to affiliates under our control, except that:

As do most catalog and Internet retailers, we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf. When we disclose information to these service providers, we disclose information to help them to perform their service. For example, in order to deliver products to you, we must share some information. We partner with third parties (such as the United Parcel Service) to ship products, to ensure delivery, and so that we can obtain feedback, improve the quality of our service, and measure and improve the quality of the service of the third party. In the example of shippers, we provide them some personally identifiable information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number.

Similarly, to help you buy products and provide customer service to you, we must provide your credit card number to financial-services corporations such as credit-card processors and issuers. When we submit your credit card number for authorization, we use state-of-the-art data encryption to protect your information. (More on this below in Data Security.)

We may disclose such information in response to requests from law enforcement officials conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use the Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.

We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business. However, it’s possible that we might acquire or merge with or be acquired by another company or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets. If that happens, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the Privacy Policy then in effect.

We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any user.

#### DATA SECURITY

Baby Tula incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) for all financial transactions through our Site. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. 

While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline.

#### CONSENT TO TRANSFER 

Baby Tula is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Site or providing us with your information, you hereby consent to this transfer. In addition, if you provide data to us about other individuals (such as your message recipients), you agree that you have obtained consent from each such individual to the submission and processing of such information under the terms of this Privacy Policy, including without limitation the transfer of such data to the United States. Although we will collect and use your information only as stated in this Privacy Policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in the United States may not be as stringent as those in some users' home jurisdictions. 

#### OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS

Upon your request, Baby Tula will remove your Personal Information from Baby Tula’s records related to this Site. This may cancel your subscription to some or all of the email communication and promotional materials offered by Baby Tula, via this Site or otherwise. If you wish to update/correct Personal Information you have already provided to us, or if you wish to remove your Personal Information from our records, please send your request to us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or via postal mail at: Baby Tula, Customer Relations, Privacy Policy, 2640 Financial Court, San Diego, CA 92117

You may choose to opt out of receiving marketing emails from us at any time by sending your request to us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or via postal mail at the address listed above, or by using the means (such as clicking “unsubscribe”) provided in our marketing emails. Please note, however, that your opt-out will apply only to marketing emails, not email communications about your order or other non-marketing correspondence.

#### OFFLINE COLLECTION, USE & DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

This Privacy Policy applies only to online collection of personal information. We also may collect information offline, where we also try to protect the privacy of your personal information. One example involves someone calling us to place an order or to ask questions. When someone calls, we will ask only for the personal information we need in order to place the order or to answer the question. When we need to store information (such as order information), we will enter it into our database through SSL encryption.  External Links: If any of our Site links you to other Web sites or mobile applications, those Web sites and mobile applications do not operate under this privacy policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other Web sites and mobile applications to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

#### UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on our Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ef878a839faf8d8e8d969b9a838ec18c8082) or via postal mail at: Baby Tula, Customer Relations, Privacy Policy, 2640 Financial Court, San Diego, CA 92117.
